<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Horizon Home Finders</string>
    <string name="log_in"><u>Log In</u></string>

    <string name="btnTextJonell">WhatsApp Jonéll</string>
    <string name="btnTextSaveena">WhatsApp Saveena</string>
    <string name="btnTextSune">WhatsApp Suné</string>
    <string name="btnDial">Phone Office</string>
    <string name="btnContact">Contact Details</string>
    <string name="btnAddListing">Add Listing</string>
    <string name="btnBackClientHome">Back</string>

    <string name="txtText">WhatsApp Agent</string>
    <string name="txtDial">Phone Agent</string>
    <string name="publish_a_new_property">Publish A New Property</string>
    <string name="reach_thousands_of_buyers_or_renters_ninstantly">Reach thousands of buyers or renters \ninstantly!</string>
    <string name="intent">Intent</string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>

    <!-- Provinces -->
    <string-array name="provinces">
        <item>Province</item>
        <item>Eastern Cape</item>
        <item>Free State</item>
        <item>Gauteng</item>
        <item>KwaZulu-Natal</item>
        <item>Limpopo</item>
        <item>Mpumalanga</item>
        <item>Northern Cape</item>
        <item>North West</item>
        <item>Western Cape</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Eastern Cape -->
    <string-array name="eastern_cape_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Butterworth</item>
        <item>Dikeni</item>
        <item>East London</item>
        <item>Gqeberha</item>
        <item>Graaff-Reinet</item>
        <item>Kariega</item>
        <item>Komani</item>
        <item>Makhanda</item>
        <item>Mthatha</item>
        <item>Qonce</item>
        <item>Zwelitsha</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Free State -->
    <string-array name="free_state_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Bethlehem</item>
        <item>Bloemfontein</item>
        <item>Jagersfontein</item>
        <item>Kroonstad</item>
        <item>Odendaalsrus</item>
        <item>Parys</item>
        <item>Phuthaditjhaba</item>
        <item>Sasolburg</item>
        <item>Virginia</item>
        <item>Welkom</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Gauteng -->
    <string-array name="gauteng_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Benoni</item>
        <item>Boksburg</item>
        <item>Brakpan</item>
        <item>Carletonville</item>
        <item>Germiston</item>
        <item>Johannesburg</item>
        <item>Krugersdorp</item>
        <item>Pretoria</item>
        <item>Randburg</item>
        <item>Randfontein</item>
        <item>Roodepoort</item>
        <item>Soweto</item>
        <item>Springs</item>
        <item>Vanderbijlpark</item>
        <item>Vereeniging</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for KZN -->
    <string-array name="kwazulu_natal_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Durban</item>
        <item>Empangeni</item>
        <item>Newcastle</item>
        <item>Pietermaritzburg</item>
        <item>Pinetown</item>
        <item>Ulundi</item>
        <item>Umlazi</item>
        <item>uMnambithi</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Limpopo -->
    <string-array name="limpopo_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Giyani</item>
        <item>Lebowakgomo</item>
        <item>Musina</item>
        <item>Phalaborwa</item>
        <item>Polokwane</item>
        <item>Seshego</item>
        <item>Sibasa</item>
        <item>Thabazimbi</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Mpumalanga -->
    <string-array name="mpumalanga_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Emalahleni</item>
        <item>Mbombela</item>
        <item>Secunda</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for North West -->
    <string-array name="north_west_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Klerksdorp</item>
        <item>Mahikeng</item>
        <item>Mmabatho</item>
        <item>Potchefstroom</item>
        <item>Rustenburg</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Northern Cape -->
    <string-array name="northern_cape_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Kimberley</item>
        <item>Kuruman</item>
        <item>Port Nolloth</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example Cities for Western Cape -->
    <string-array name="western_cape_cities">
        <item>City</item>
        <item>Bellville</item>
        <item>Cape Town</item>
        <item>George</item>
        <item>Hopefield</item>
        <item>Oudtshoorn</item>
        <item>Paarl</item>
        <item>Simon’s Town</item>
        <item>Stellenbosch</item>
        <item>Swellendam</item>
        <item>Worcester</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- All Example Cities -->
    <string-array name="cities">
        <item>Bellville</item>
        <item>Benoni</item>
        <item>Bethlehem</item>
        <item>Bloemfontein</item>
        <item>Boksburg</item>
        <item>Brakpan</item>
        <item>Butterworth</item>
        <item>Cape Town</item>
        <item>Carletonville</item>
        <item>Dikeni</item>
        <item>Durban</item>
        <item>East London</item>
        <item>Emalahleni</item>
        <item>Empangeni</item>
        <item>George</item>
        <item>Germiston</item>
        <item>Giyani</item>
        <item>Gqeberha</item>
        <item>Graaff-Reinet</item>
        <item>Hopefield</item>
        <item>Jagersfontein</item>
        <item>Johannesburg</item>
        <item>Kariega</item>
        <item>Kimberley</item>
        <item>Klerksdorp</item>
        <item>Komani</item>
        <item>Kroonstad</item>
        <item>Krugersdorp</item>
        <item>Kuruman</item>
        <item>Lebowakgomo</item>
        <item>Mahikeng</item>
        <item>Makhanda</item>
        <item>Mbombela</item>
        <item>Mmabatho</item>
        <item>Mthatha</item>
        <item>Musina</item>
        <item>Newcastle</item>
        <item>Odendaalsrus</item>
        <item>Oudtshoorn</item>
        <item>Paarl</item>
        <item>Parys</item>
        <item>Phalaborwa</item>
        <item>Phuthaditjhaba</item>
        <item>Pietermaritzburg</item>
        <item>Pinetown</item>
        <item>Polokwane</item>
        <item>Port Nolloth</item>
        <item>Potchefstroom</item>
        <item>Pretoria</item>
        <item>Qonce</item>
        <item>Randburg</item>
        <item>Randfontein</item>
        <item>Roodepoort</item>
        <item>Rustenburg</item>
        <item>Sasolburg</item>
        <item>Secunda</item>
        <item>Seshego</item>
        <item>Sibasa</item>
        <item>Simon’s Town</item>
        <item>Soweto</item>
        <item>Springs</item>
        <item>Stellenbosch</item>
        <item>Swellendam</item>
        <item>Thabazimbi</item>
        <item>Ulundi</item>
        <item>Umlazi</item>
        <item>Vanderbijlpark</item>
        <item>Vereeniging</item>
        <item>Virginia</item>
        <item>Welkom</item>
        <item>Worcester</item>
        <item>Zwelitsha</item>
        <item>uMnambithi</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="privacy_policy">PRIVACY POLICY\n
Last updated November 03, 2024\n\n\n
This Privacy Notice for Horizon Home Finders (‘we’, ‘us’, or ‘our’), describes how and why we might access, collect, store, use, and/or share (‘process’) your personal information when you use our services (‘Services’), including when you:\n\n
 • Download and use our mobile application (Horizon Home Finders), or any other application of ours that links to this Privacy Notice.\n
 • Use Buying and selling of property in South Africa. This mobile application’s purpose is to provide an efficient digital platform for property owners to sell or rent out their properties, and for property seeking individuals to find the perfect property that fits their needs and budget. Agents are the intermediaries between sellers and buyers, making the transactions as efficient as possible.\n
 • Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events.\n
Questions or concerns? Reading this Privacy Notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. We are responsible for making decisions about how your personal information is processed. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at s224032704@mandela.ac.za .\n\n

SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS\n
This summary provides key points from our Privacy Notice, but you can find out more details about any of those topics by using our table of contents below to find the section you are looking for.\n\n
What personal information do we process?\n
When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process personal information depending on how you interact with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. Learn more about personal information you disclose to us.\n\n
Do we process any sensitive personal information?\n
Some of the information may be considered ‘special’ or ‘sensitive’ in certain jurisdictions, for example your racial or ethnic origins, sexual orientation, and religious beliefs. We do not process sensitive personal information.\n\n
Do we collect any information from third parties?\n
We do not collect any information from third parties.\n\n
How do we process your information?\n
We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent. We process your information only when we have a valid legal reason to do so. Learn more about how we process your information.\n\n
In what situations and with which types of parties do we share personal information?\n
We may share information in specific situations and with specific categories of third parties. Learn more about when and with whom we share your personal information.\n\n
How do we keep your information safe?\n
We have adequate organisational and technical processes and procedures in place to protect your personal information. However, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorised third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Learn more about how we keep your information safe.\n\n
What are your rights?\n
Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean you have certain rights regarding your personal information Learn more about your privacy rights.\n\n
How do you exercise your rights?\nThe easiest way to exercise your rights is by submitting a data subject access request, or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.\n\n
Want to learn more about what we do with any information we collect? Review the Privacy Notice in full.\n\n

TABLE OF CONTENTS\n
1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?\n
2. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?\n
3. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?\n
4. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?\n
5. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?\n
6. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?\n
7. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?\n
8. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?\n
9. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES\n
10. DO OTHER REGIONS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?\n
11. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?\n
12. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?\n
13. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?\n\n

1. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?\n
Personal information you disclose to us\n
In Short: We collect personal information that you provide to us.\n
We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Services, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us.\n
Personal Information Provided by You. The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may Include the following:\n
 • names\n
• email addresses\n
• phone numbers\n
• usernames\n
• passwords\n
• locations\n
Sensitive Information. We do not process sensitive Information.\n
Application Data. If you use our application(s), we also may collect the following information if you choose to provide us with access or permission:\n
• Geolocation Information.\n
We may request access or permission to track location-based information from your mobile device, either continuously or while you are using our mobile application(s), to provide certain location-based services. If you wish to change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device\'s settings.\n
This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our application(s), for troubleshooting, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.\n
All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.\n
Google API\n
Our use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to Google API Services User Data Policy, including the Limited Use requirements.\n\n

2. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?\n
In Short: We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent.\n
We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:\n
• To facilitate account creation and authentication and otherwise manage user accounts. We may process your information so you can create and log in to your account, as well as keep your account in working order.\n
• To deliver and facilitate delivery of services to the user. We may process your information to provide you with the requested service.\n
• To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users. We may process your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the requested service.\n
• To enable user-to-user communications. We may process your information if you choose to use any of our offerings that allow for communication with another user.\n
• To request feedback. We may process your information when necessary to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Services.\n
• To protect our Services. We may process your information as part of our efforts to keep our Services safe and secure, including fraud monitoring and prevention.\n
• To evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing, and your experience. We may process your information when we believe it is necessary to identify usage trends, determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and to evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing, and your experience.\n
• To identify usage trends. We may process information about how you use our Services to better understand how they are being used so we can improve them.\n
• To comply with our legal obligations. We may process your information to comply with our legal obligations, respond to legal requests, and exercise, establish, or defend our legal rights.\n\n

3. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?\n
In Short: We may share information in specific situations described in this section and/or with the following categories of third parties.\n
Vendors, Consultants, and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents (‘third parties’) who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. We have contracts in place with our third parties, which are designed to help safeguard your personal information. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will also not share your personal information with any organisation apart from us, they also commit to protect the data they hold on our behalf and to retain it for the period we instruct.\n
The categories of third parties we may share personal information with are as follows:\n
• Communication &amp; Collaboration Tools\n
• Sales &amp; Marketing Tools\n
We also may need to share your personal information in the following situations:\n
• Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.\n
• When we use Google Maps Platform APIs. We may share your information with certain Google Maps Platform APIs (e.g. Google Maps APl, Places API). Google Maps uses GPS, Wi-Fi, and cell towers to estimate your location. GPS is accurate to about 20 meters, while Wi-Fi and cell towers help improve accuracy when GPS signals are weak, like indoors. This data helps Google Maps provide directions, but it is not always perfectly precise.\n
• Affiliates. We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honour this Privacy Notice. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.\n
• Business Partners. We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services, or promotions.\n
• Other Users. When you share personal information (for example, by posting comments, contributions, or other content to the Services) or otherwise interact with public areas of the Services, such personal information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly made available outside the Services in perpetuity. Similarly, other users will be able to view descriptions of your activity, communicate with you within our Services, and view your profile.\n\n

4. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?\m
In Short: We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information.\n
We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to gather information when you interact with our Services. Some online tracking technologies help us maintain the security of our Services and your account, prevent crashes, fix bugs, save your preferences, and assist with basic site functions.\n
We also permit third parties and service providers to use online tracking technologies on our Services for analytics and advertising, including to help manage and display advertisements, to tailor advertisements to your interests, or to send abandoned shopping cart reminders (depending on your communication preferences). The third parties and service providers use their technology to provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests which may appear either on our Services or on other websites.\n
Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Notice.\n\n

5. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?\n
In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Notice unless otherwise required by law.\n
We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.\n
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.\n\n

6. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?\n
In Short: We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organisational and technical security measures.\n
We have implemented appropriate and reasonable technical and organisational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorised third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.\n\n

7. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?\n
In Short: We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age.\n
We do not knowingly collect, solicit data from, or market to children under 18 years of age, nor do we knowingly sell such personal information. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent's use of the Services. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we may have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at s224032704@mandela.ac.za. \n\n

8. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?\n
In Short: You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time, depending on your country, province, or state of residence.\n
Withdrawing your consent: if we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, which may be express and/or implied consent depending on the applicable law, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section ‘HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?’ below.\n
However, please note that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal nor, when applicable law allows, will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.\n
Account Information\n
If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:\n
• Log in to your account settings and update your user account.\n
Upon your request to terminate your account we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our legal terms and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.\n
If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at s224032704@mandela.ac.za .\n\n

9. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES\n
Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (‘DNT’) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage, no uniform technology standard for recognising and implementing DNT signals has been finalised. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Notice.\n\n

10. DO OTHER REGIONS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?\n
In Short: You may have additional rights based on the country you reside in.\n
Republic of South Africa\n
At any time, you have the right to request access to or correction of your personal information. You can make such a request by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section ‘HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?’\n
If you are unsatisfied with the manner in which we address any complaint with regard to our processing of personal information, you can contact the office of the regulator, the details of which are:\n
The Information Regulator (South Africa)\n
General enquiries: enquiries@inforegulator.org.za\n
Complaints (complete POPIA/PAIA form 5): PAIAComplaints@inforegulator.org.za &amp; POPIAComplaints@inforegulator.org.za\n\n

11. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?\n
In Short: Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.\n
We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated ‘Revised’ date at the top of this Privacy Notice. If we make material changes to this Privacy Notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this Privacy Notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.\n\n

12. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?\n
If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at s224032704@mandela.ac.za or contact us by post at:\n
 Horizon Home Finders\n
PO Box 77000\n
Nelson Mandela University\n
Gqeberha, Eastern Cape 6031\n
South Africa\n\n

13. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?\n
You have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, details about how we have processed it, correct inaccuracies, or delete your personal information. You may also have the right to withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information. These rights may be limited in some circumstances by applicable law. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please fill out and submit a data subject access request.
</string>

</resources>
